人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   小萌
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第九集
圣诞节七天前的一个清晨
I saw three kids come sailing through
我看见三个小孩从眼前飘过
on seven days before Christmas in the morning.
你挂忍者飞镖干嘛
Why are you putting up ninja throwing stars?
我还以为是蛋糕垫纸
I think they're doilies.
是雪花
They're snowflakes!
多有圣诞节气氛啊
They're Christmas-y.
忍者雪花
Ninja snowflakes!
吉恩
Gene.
说到圣诞节  这是我今年的礼品清单
Speaking of Christmas, here's my annual list of demands.
"我自己的公寓"
"My own apartment."
工作室可不行哦
And it cannot be a studio.
你还有七天的时间去购置
You have exactly seven shopping days to comply.
如果到了第八天还没办好
If it rolls into day eight,
就等着我号啕大哭不依不饶吧
there will be tears and violence.
我想要一个白板
I want a dry erase board.
阴茎捕蝇器
这样我就能写下我所有的私密想法
So I can write down all my private thoughts
然后立马擦掉
and then erase them immediately.
我想要电影《冰上轻驰》里
I want the actual Olympic bobsled
演员用的奥林匹克雪橇
used in Cool Runnings.
我们哪样都买不起  孩子们
We can't afford any of those things, kids.
连白板也买不起吗
Not even a dry erase board?
买不起  蒂娜
No, Tina!
抱歉  由于"城市指南"把我们的店
Sorry. Been a tough year,
错列为加油站  今年过得举步维艰
ever since the City Guide listed us as a gas station.
礼物不是重点
Hey, a bunch of presents don't matter.
收礼物不是圣诞节的全部意义所在
Christmas isn't all about getting stuff.
是的  就是
Yes, it is!
收回你说的话  收回你说的话
Take it back! Take it back!
圣诞快乐  迈克
Merry Christmas, Mike!
也祝你圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas to you.
-你好  迈克  -你好  鲍勃
- Hi, Mike. - Hi, Bob.
给你邮件
Here's your mail.
多谢
Thanks.
怎么了
What?
对了  当然了
Oh. Right. Of course.
我总是不知道该给邮递员多少小费
You know, I never know how much to tip the mailman.
是  你是不知道
No, you don't.
给你这个
Um, you know what, here.
我在这张纸上写个数字
Uh, I am going to write a number on this piece of paper.
你看看
There you go.
如果说我一周只送一天信
Oh, yeah, that's about right--
这个数还差不多
if I delivered mail one day a week.
好吧  再多给你点
Fine. Here's more than that.
多谢  鲍勃
Oh, thanks, Bob.
我也给你准备了份特殊的礼物
Hey, I got something special for you, too.
特快专递
Special delivery.
要是我不给小费你就不打算把它给我了吗
Were you not gonna give me this if I didn't tip you?
不  我会给的  只是不是今天给
No, I-I would have. Just not today.
也许是圣诞老人的来信
Maybe it's from Santa.
是3B律师所寄来的
It's from the law firm of Bankoff, Bostwick & Biel.
圣诞老人起诉了我们
Santa's suing us!
信上说欧内斯特・伦巴第在遗嘱中
Hey, it says I've been named an heir
指定我为继承人
in the enclosed will of Ernest G. Lombard.
欧叔叔死了吗
Aw! Uncle Ernie's dead?
但现在是圣诞节啊
But it's Christmas.
我和欧叔叔都好多年没说过话了
Huh, I haven't talked to Uncle Ernie in years.
"跟欧叔叔谈谈"可以用作上大号的暗号
"Talking to Uncle Ernie" would be great code for going a poop.
吉恩  他刚刚去世了
Gene, he just died.
我刚刚那句是颂词来着
It's a fitting tribute.
不好意思  这人是谁
Excuse me, who is/was this guy?
是我母亲的兄弟
He was my mother's brother.
他开了巴第百货商店
He owned Lombard's Department Store
后来大型购物商场的出现让他破了产
before the mall came and put it out of business.
欧叔叔给你留了多少钱
How much did Uncle Ernie leave you?
我们看看信上怎么说
Well, let's see what it say
别看
A-ba-ba-ba! Don't look!
我们来读读遗嘱
Let's have a reading of the will.
我去做潘趣酒[一种低酒精的饮料酒]
I'll make punch.
你永远想做潘趣酒
You always want to make punch.
就没听说过蛋酒吗
Ever heard of eggnog?
我有好多潘趣酒的试饮包
I have all those sample punch packets.
看  我刚又得到一包
Ah, look, I got-- just got another one.
我太激动了  我得去跟欧叔叔谈谈
I'm so excited! I have to go talk to Uncle Ernie!
好了  大家都分到潘趣酒了
Okay, everyone has their punch,
是时候来继承点什么东西了
so it's time to inherit the wind!
味道不错
Oh, mmm. Ooh, it's good.
不  不怎么样
No, it's not.
我们做个约定吧
Let's make a pact
不要让金钱改变我们
that we won't let the money change us.
欧叔叔最糟糕的圣诞节
Uncle Ernie's worst Christmas
将会是我们最棒的圣诞节
is going to be our best Christmas!
我们先别高兴得太早
Okay, let's not get ahead of ourselves.
-牙买加雪橇  -公寓
- Jamaican bobsled! - Apartment!
白板
Dry erase board.
说得就是你们
Uh, like that.
只能说今年的圣诞节也许没那么糟
Let's just say this Christmas might not be terrible.
你要继承的是
You have been bequeathed...
击鼓声
Drumroll!
昆西大道的第39号仓库"尽管装"
...storage unit 39 at the Quincy Avenue Just-Stow-It.
"尽管装"仓库
我还是抱着很大的期望
I still have a good feeling about this.
里面也许有一辆古董车
There could be an old car in there.
或者一屋子貂皮大衣
Or a whole bunch of fur coats.
那我就要往衣服上扔颜料
I'm gonna throw paint on them!
记住  如果里面真是好东西
Remember, if it's something really good,
我们还要为此付税款
we'll have to pay taxes on it.
我们得到一个穴居人
We won a caveman!
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫切特
My name's Chet.
切斯特的缩写  切的全称
Uh, short for Chester, long for Ch.
这是我的一个小玩笑
That's my little joke.
你们喜欢这个笑话吗
Did you, did you enjoy the joke?
不错
Yes.
我是蒂娜  用脱鞋吗
I'm Tina. Shoes on or off?
不用脱鞋  请进  来点喝的吗
On, please. Can I get you something to drink?
要止咳糖浆还是雨水
Cough syrup? Rainwater?
不是那个  那是尿
Not that. That's urine.
你为什么会住在我叔叔的仓库里
Why are you living in my uncle's storage unit?
伦巴第先生是你叔叔吗
Mr. Lombard is your uncle?
是的  他在遗嘱中将这间屋子留给了我
Yeah, he left me this unit in his will.
伦巴第先生去去世了吗
Oh. Mr. Lombard's dead?
是的
Yeah.
进来抱抱吗
You want to come in for a hug?
不用了
Um, no.
为什么  因为我们是初次相见吗
Why? 'Cause we just met?
是的  我想是
Yeah, I guess.
这样好些了
That's better.
-我能也抱抱吗  -不行
- May I join you two? - No.
你是怎么认识欧叔叔的
So, how'd you know Uncle Ernie?
我在他的商店做橱窗秀已经二十年了
I did window displays at his store for 20 years.
商店倒闭后  他让我住在这里
When the store closed, he let me stay in here.
你怎么没和家人朋友待在一起
Don't you have a family or friends to stay with?
圣诞节快到了啊
You know, with Christmas coming and all that.
等等  到圣诞节了吗
Wait, it's Christmas?
我的日历上现在是  八月啊
My calendar says it's, uh, da-da-da... August.
鲍鲍  跟他说他可以住我们的地下室
Bobby, tell him he can stay in our basement.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
就因为  这个时机嘛
Because, 'tis the season!
什么时机  带陌生人到地下室的时机么
Of what? Taking strange men into our basement?
做好事的时机  鲍鲍
Of being nice, Bobby.
他在这里挺好
He's fine right here.
有电视  还有个罐子
He's got a TV and a jar.
-你们悄悄话的声音有够大的  -抱歉
- You guys are loud whisperers. - Sorry.
所以你们要帮忙还房租吗
So, you're taking over the lease?
150美金一个月
It's 150 a month.
再次感谢你们让我住在这里
Thanks again for letting me stay here.
鲍鲍  你这个老好人
Yeah, Bobby, you old softie.
你就像个多情的雪人
You're like a mushy snowman.
地方真大
A lot of space!
我都等不及想给它铺上地毯了
I can't wait until the carpeting comes in.
你们确定墙壁要涂这种颜色吗
Is your heart set on this wall color?
我倒是有一些好主意
'Cause I have some ideas.
声明在先  切特
But just to be clear, Chet, you're only here
你只能待到过完圣诞节
till right after Christmas.
-今年圣诞节吗  -是的
- This Christmas? - Um, yeah.
再一周就到了
The one that's coming up in a week.
从来没有人对我这么好过
This is the nicest thing anybody's ever done for me.
包括给我这身运动服的塞尔
Including when Sal over there gave me this track suit.
如果你想送塞尔东西
If you want to give Sal something,
他需要一个小鸡鸡
he needs a penis.
圣诞节前六天
-着火了  -什么
- Fire! - What?!
-开个玩笑  快来看看  -咋了
- Just kidding. Come look. - What?
-快来  -啥  发生什么事了
- Come on. - What? What happened?
切特走了
Chet's gone.
他的尿壶凉了
His pee jar is cold.
终于可以松一口气了
I got to say, I'm relieved.
那家伙感觉怪怪的
There was something off about that guy.
身上还有一股...
And he smelled...
是切特
Oh, oh! It's Chet!
嗨  切特
Oh. Hey, Chet.
原来你在这儿啊
There's my guy.
你们觉得这个秀怎么样
What do you think of the display?
有节日的气氛不
Is it holi-doing it for you?
这都是你一个人做的吗
You did all this?
太棒了
Oh, it's amazing!
你们好心收留了我  我的报答是
You gave me a place to stay, I give you:
橱窗里的课堂  切特作品
Class under Glass, by Chet.
这么说你不光是设计者  还是参与者咯
So you don't just design the displays, you're also in them?
当然  有何不可呢
Of course. Why wouldn't I be?
秀不错
Well, it's a nice display.
谢谢你
Um, thanks for doing it.
你花了多久
How long did it take...?
切特  切特
Chet? Chet?
他又变的怪怪的了
He's being weird again.
都两个小时了  他一点没动
It's been two hours and he still hasn't moved.
走你
Come on!
我脱他裤子都脱烦了
I'm tired of pantsing him.
好像我脱的是石头
It's like pantsing a stone.
或者是爷爷
Or Grandpa.
我喜欢你们的橱窗秀
I love your display.
帽子真不错
The hats are fabulous.
怎么卖
How much are they?
我们不卖帽子
Uh, we don't sell hats.
我们卖的是汉堡
We sell burgers.
我们还得买一顶帽子
We still need to find a hat
再给邮递员选份礼物
and something for the mailman.
你们总卖礼品券吧
Please tell me you sell gift certificates.
有笔和纸巾  我可以写一张给你
I, uh, I have a napkin and a pen, so I can write one.
切特人是怪了点
You know, Chet may be a strange guy,
但他的橱窗秀可是让客人多了不少
but his display really upped our foot traffic.
好了  切特  我们打烊了
Okay, Chet. We're closed.
你可以动了
You can move now.
真是浑身酸痛
I am full of lactic acid
不过我已经想到明天橱窗秀的点子啦
and ideas for tomorrow's window!
你明天还要弄一个新的吗
Ah! You're gonna do a different one tomorrow?
明天  后天  大后天
Tomorrow and then the next day and then the next day
大大后天  大大大后天
and then the next day and then the next day
接着就是圣诞了  我就不做了
and then it's Christmas, so I'll stop.
我们能帮忙不  我要当吉恩模型
Can we help? I want to be a Gene-equin!
我当蒂娜模特
I'll be a Tina-quin.
那我去印点真的礼品券
Let me print up some real gift certificates.
再用一张大窗帘把橱窗遮起来
And maybe, uh, cover the window with a big curtain,
等我们开张前再拉开
and unveil the new display right before we open.
很有戏剧效果  你是同性恋么
That's very theatrical. Are you gay?
我们倒是想
We wish.
那么
Okay.
有没有找到适合明天的秀的东西呀
Anything jumping out at you for tomorrow's display?
我找到一列火车
I found a train!
玩具们最先进的旅行工具
The most civilized form of toy travel.
这放在我的新公寓里应该不错
This would look good in my new apartment.
我本来是说着玩的  现在却有点期待了
It was a joke at first, but now I'm starting to expect it.
团队合作  感觉真不赖
This is fun, teaming up, you know?
我以前都是和我妻子纳丁一起做
I used to do windows with my wife, Nadine.
你结婚了吗
Oh, you're married?
我们分开了
We're separated.
没关系的  过去的就让它过去吧
It's okay. What's past is past.
还是把精力放在明天的秀上吧
Let's just, uh, focus on tomorrow's window.
向前看
Moving on!
是啊  你的新家人可不想
Yeah, your new family doesn't want
听你讲旧家人的事
to hear about your old family.
*在我还小的时候  我相信有圣诞老人*
*When I was small, I believed in Santa Claus*
*虽然我知道那是我老爸扮的*
*Though I knew it was my dad*
*我会在圣诞节挂起长筒袜*
*And I would hang up my stocking at Christmas*
*拆开礼物我就会很开心*
*Open my presents and I'd be glad*
*圣诞老人  给我们点零用钱*
*Father Christmas, give us some money...*
在当地一家开心汉堡店的橱窗里
One local man has gone from homeless to "Homeful"
一个流浪汉找到了容身之处
here in the window of Bob's Burgers,
从画面可以看到
where you could say he's been making
他正在进行一场活人橱窗秀
quite a living display of himself.
快看  我可以看到自己诶
Hey, look, I can see me!
看  我招手了
Look, I'm waving!
太好了
Wow, this is great for us.
我们上电视了  我们的餐馆...
We're on the news. The restaurant...
吉恩  别舔自己了
Gene, stop licking yourself.
你现在在上电视呢
You're on TV.
我早就该上了
Where I belong!
那么  鲍勃
So, Bob, what's it gonna be
圣诞夜的终极秀是什么呢
for the big Christmas Eve finale?
我不知道终极秀会是什么
I don't know what the last display's gonna be.
切特才是策划人
Chet's the idea guy.
给我们讲讲你的策划吧  切特
Let's hear your idea, Chet.
不  不  不  别告诉我
No, no, no! Don't tell me!
保持点神秘感
Don't ruin it.
算了  你还是告诉我吧
No, you got to tell me, you...
我忍不了了
I can't handle it.
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no!
别说  别说
Don't tell me. Don't tell me.
跟他讲话真有意思
Guy's fun to talk to.
不管是什么  最好很精彩
Whatever it is, it better be good.
莫特的妈妈要来看呢
Mort's mom is coming to see it.
她有白内障  所以最好做得大一点
She's got cataracts, so make it big.
虽然这会儿还太早  我还是想说
It's not here yet, but I want to go on record and say
这是有史以来最棒的圣诞节了
this is the best Christmas ever! Whoa!
是啊  搞不好我们可以给孩子们
I know. We might actually be able to afford
买点像样的礼物了呢
to buy the kids something nice.
要不我一会儿溜出去买  你帮我掩护
And maybe I can sneak out later while you cover for me.
好呀  我就告诉孩子们
Yeah, I'll tell the kids
你去给你的情妇买礼物了
you're dropping off a present for your mistress.
才怪咧
As if.
你包遥控器干嘛
Why are you wrapping the TV remote?
是我给老爸的圣诞礼物
It's my Christmas present to Dad.
他爱死这玩意儿了
He loves this thing.
好主意
Great idea.
那我就包老妈的眼镜
I'll wrap Mom's glasses.
切特  你在看什么
Hey, what you looking at, Chet?
我只是在放空
I'm just zoning out.
这首是纳丁最爱的圣诞歌曲
This was Nadine's favorite Christmas song.
纳丁是谁
Oh, who's Nadine?
*平安夜*
*Silent night*
*圣善夜*
*Holy night...*
纳丁是谁
Who's Nadine?
切特的前妻
She's Chet's ex-wife.
他很想念她
He's missing her pretty bad.
怎么能不想呢
How could you not miss her?
她真美
Oh, she's gorgeous!
等下  她是
Wait, is she...?
她看上去还不错
She looks nice.
姿势很完美
Yeah, perfect posture.
胸部还是木头做的
And wooden boobs.
切特  这是人体模型
Chet, this is a mannequin.
我和纳丁结婚那会儿我也是模型来着
Back when Nadine and I got married, I was a mannequin, too.
这下我懂了
Oh, now I understand.
你以为自己是人体模型
You think you were a mannequin?
没关系的  你们不用害怕
Oh, it's okay. You don't need to be scared of me.
我又不是杀人人体模型
I'm not one of those murder mannequins
也不是恶魔人体模型
or satanic mannequins.
我就是个商店人体模型  后来变成了人
I'm just a store mannequin that came to life.
你住我家地下室  真是太荣幸了
So happy you're staying with us in our basement.
*静享天赐安眠*
*Sleep in heavenly...*
好了  都出去
Okay, everybody out.
切特疯了  琳
Chet's crazy, Lin.
你觉得他会在圣诞节之前还是之后动手
Do you think he'll kill us before or after Christmas?
他不会杀人啦
I don't think he will.
他说了他不是杀人人体模型啊
He said he's not a murder mannequin.
你俩真得练习练习怎么说悄悄话
You two really have to work on your whispering.
你要是人体模型  应该感觉不到这个吧
So, if you're a mannequin, you won't feel this!
好痛
That hurt!
我只说我曾经是人体模型
I didn't say I am a mannequin.
没说现在还是
I said I was a mannequin.
我明白了
I get it.
突然有一天
One day, all of a sudden,
你就有了人的生理结构
you're anatomically correct.
我刚刚经历那个阶段
I just went through that.
我十分确定人体模型是不会变成人的
Well, I'm pretty sure mannequins don't turn into people,
除了在电影《木头美人》里
except in that one movie.
这不是发生在电影里
This was no movie.
而是在零售商店里
This was retail.
那时刚上夏季运动衫新款  纳丁出现了
The new summer sportswear had just come in, and so had Nadine.
她没有乳头  也没有"小弟弟"
She didn't have nipples, and, brother,
这些她也用不着
she didn't need them.
等到夏秋交替  休闲装上市之时
As summer turned to fall casuals,
我们的关系早已非比寻常而且绝不
our relationship became anything but.
随便
Casual?
casual既有"休闲装"之意 也可表示"随便 非正式"
没错  绝不随便
Yes, casual.
那年冬天  我带纳丁去滑雪
That winter, I took Nadine skiing.
一场悲剧就此发生
There was a terrible accident.
纳丁摔碎了她的右手
Nadine shattered her right hand.
我的天
Oh, God.
当她被接了两只左手后重回商场之时
When she came back to the store with two left hands,
我便立刻做了一个决定
I knew I had to make a decision.
将哪只手换成钩子
Which hand to replace with a hook?
不  将戒指戴在哪只手上
No. Which one to put the ring on.
我的天  琳  你哭了吗
Oh, God, Lin, are you crying?
你也知道我对婚礼没抵抗力
You know I love weddings.
我们本来要永远在一起的  谁知道
We were going to be together forever. Then came...
大型购物商场出现了
the mall.
大型购物商场去死吧
Damn that mall!
伦巴第决定清仓处理
Lombard's had an everything-must-go sale,
我的一切也随之而去
and my everything went.
大甩卖 库存6到8折起  清仓大处理
之后我再没见过她
I never saw her again.
等等  为什么她不需要乳头
Wait, why didn't she need nipples?
我那个心碎的啊
I was so heartbroken.
简直是痛彻心扉  一定是这样
The pain must have turned me human,
一定是这样我才会变成人
so I could feel pain.
这真是有史以来最伟大的爱情故事
This is the greatest love story ever told.
听着  切特  这不可能是真的
Look, Chet, there's no way any of that could be true.
那你说  要是我以前不是人体模型
Well then, if I wasn't a mannequin,
怎么可能不会用电脑呢
how come I don't know how to use a computer?
你倒是解释看看啊  鲍勃
Explain that, Bob.
就是  老爸  解释吧
Yeah, Dad, explain that.
别放弃  切特
Don't give up, Chet.
也许纳丁还流浪在外  你会找到她的
Maybe Nadine's still out there. You could find her.
可她长了那么一张俊脸
Hmm. Well, with a face like that,
八成是去巴黎或者米兰当模特了
I assume she's modeling in Paris or Milan.
我们可以帮忙
We could help,
就算要去巴黎或米兰也没关系
even if it means going to Paris or Milan.
我赌她在科索沃
Right. I bet she's in Kosovo.
不准你们去帮切特找什么人体模型
No one's helping Chet look for a mannequin
真正有没有这玩意还不一定呢
who may or may not exist.
-怎么没有  -好吧  你说有就有
- She existed! - Fine, she existed.
而且你还和她相爱过
And you were in love with her.
那你也不会是人体模型  切特
But you were never a mannequin, Chet.
往前看吧
Just move on.
纳丁这会儿搞不好在哪个垃圾场躺着呢
Nadine is probably in a dump somewhere.
天哪
Oh, God!
孩子们  上床睡觉  马上
Kids, bed-- now.
我要和你们父亲好好谈谈
I want to talk to your father.
别走  孩子们  留下来
No, kids, stay. Please stay.
-出去  出去  -别走  别走
- Go. Go! - Stay. Stay!
-都出去  -吉恩  别走
- You go! - Gene, stay!
-赶紧地  -蒂娜  站那儿别动
- Now! - Tina, don't move!
-你出去  -露易丝  别走
- You go! - Louise, stay!
-都给我出去  -别留下我一个人
- Get out of here! - Don't leave me!
你们给我出去
You get out of here!
你怎么能当着可怜的切特的面说那种话
How could you say that in front of that poor Chet?
可怜个屁  被他纠缠的我们才可怜咧
Poor Chet? Poor us, stuck with poor Chet.
鲍勃  你把他弄哭了
Bobby, you made him cry.
那是他情绪多变  琳
He's unstable, Lin.
能让他哭的事可多了
I'm sure lots of things make him cry.
我气得要跺脚了
Oh, I'm so mad I could stomp,
跺吧  老妈
Do it, Mom!
跳起你的跺脚舞
Do the stompy dance!
-她在跺了  -别拿槲寄生到床上来了
- She's doing it! - Don't bother bringing the mistletoe to bed!
给我拿点零食来
But do bring me a snack.
巧克力
Chocolate!
圣诞节前夕的早晨
老妈  老爸  起床了
Mom, Dad, get up.
-怎么了  -出什么事了
- What? - What happened?
快去看看切特的展窗吧
You have to see Chet's window.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这怎么回事
What the hell is it?
-他变成杀人人体模型了  -错
- He's gone murder-mannequin. - No.
它是我内心的真实写照  鲍勃
It's the display window of my soul, Bob.
我这是在警醒大家
This is a warning.
对任何事都别投入满腔爱意 信念和希望
Don't love or believe or hope in anything.
传达得很到位
Message received.
这场面我喜欢
I like this area.
再接再厉
Dig deeper.
大家马上就要来参观了
People are coming to see this.
我们的展窗可上过电视
Our window was on TV
还登过报纸的"圣诞倒数"单元
and in the newspaper's Christmas Countdown.
你得把它换成欢乐祥和那种
You have to change it. Make it happy.
我的欢乐早已被遗失在哪个垃圾场了
My happy is gone! It's in the dump somewhere.
鲍勃  我希望你听懂了
I hope your face can catch, Bob,
我在用你说过的话讽刺你
because I'm throwing your words back in it.
干得好  鲍鲍  太漂亮了
Nice job, Bobby. Way to go.
我们要找到纳丁
We have to find Nadine.
别担心
Don't worry.
吉恩模型对人体模型的想法了如指掌
Gene-equin knows how a mannequin thinks.
传统圣诞寻找人体模型之旅
Ah, a traditional Christmas mannequin hunt.
见过这个人体模型吗  电话 555-0175
拉窗帘
Show us the window!
Yeah! Show us the window!
现在
Now!
我们找到纳丁了
We found Nadine!
找到她了
We found her!
这真是圣诞奇迹
Oh, it's a Christmas miracle.
孩子们  我说过不准去找她  找它
I told you kids not to go looking for her-- I mean, it.
你还说过不准在你嘘嘘的时候
You also told me to not surprise you
去吓你呢  可你明明就爱得不行
when you're peeing, but you know you love it.
抢劫
Stick 'em up! Aah!
切特就要和他久违的爱人重逢了
Aw, Chet's going to be reunited with his long-lost love.
这种事在商店里可买不到
Can't get that at a store.
你们在哪儿找到她的
Where'd you find her?
商店
At a store.
我要砸窗了  我要砸窗了
I'm gonna break it! I'm gonna break it!
糟糕  我们要怎么办
Oh, crap. What are we going to do?
你要去找纳丁
You're going to go get Nadine.
那是你该做的  你这伤别人心的混蛋
That's what you're going to do, Old St. Dick.
在切特和爱人重逢后
Then Chet will have his lady love,
也许他会帮你搞定外面那帮人
and maybe he'll help you give those people their display.
那兴许有用
Hmm, that could work.
快去  走后门
Go! Use the back door.
那帮人我来应付  快走  快走
I'll stall the crowd. Go, go.
-拉窗帘  -没错
- Show us the window! - Yeah!
拉窗帘
Show us the window!
-现在  -拉窗...
- Now! - Show us the win...
琳达・贝尔彻为大家朗诵"圣诞诗"一首
"A Christmas Poem" By Linda Belcher.
圣诞啊  圣诞啊
Christmas, Christmas.
圣诞节啊  圣诞节
Christmas, oh, Christmas.
大家互道圣诞快乐
You Christmas you.
圣诞节啊  圣诞节
Christmas, Christmas.
圣是剩下的圣
C-h-I...
不对  圣是圣女的圣
No, C-H...
诞是诞生的诞
R-I-s-t-m-a-s.
你确定这是纳丁
Are you sure it's Nadine?
看她的双手  老爸
Look at her hands, Dad.
两只左手
Two lefties.
好了  你们在外面等着
All right, you guys stay out here.
她是我的  我在垃圾场找到的
She's mine. I found her at the dump.
谁捡到就是谁的
Finders keepers.
好吧
Okay, fine.
可是能不能借我用一下
But, um, could I... could I borrow her
晚上就还给你
just till the end of the day?
开什么玩笑  她可是活招牌
Are you kidding me? She pulls them in.
再说今天是圣诞前
And there's only one sex shopping day
最后一天的情趣用品购物日了
till Christmas.
生意可全指望这了
It's my biggest day.
-可明明就没人  -不不  有好多人
- There's nobody here. - Oh, no, no, no, there's other people.
都在后面呢
They're in the back part.
这些手指布偶都没有胳膊
These finger puppets have no arms.
看来我们得分散开他的注意力
Looks like we're going to need a diversion.
放个人按摩器
Release the personal massagers.
有蛇[暗指电影《空中蛇灾》]
Snakes on a plane!
小孩不能进来
Hey, no kids in here.
去搬纳丁
Get Nadine.
快  老爸  我们走
Come on, Dad! Let's go!
喷润滑油
Squirt the lube!
我午夜前会把她送回来的
Uh, I'll have her home by midnight!
最晚12点半
12:30 at the latest!
站住  你们这群神经病
Stop, you sickos!
-什么  -不  不是说你们
- What? - No, not you guys.
叮叮当当  叮叮当当
Bells, bells, bells, bells
叮叮叮叮  当当当当
Bells, bells, bells, bells, la, la, la, bells
叮那个当  当那个叮
La, la, la, bells, la, la, la, bells, la...
-老妈  老妈  -咋  咋  咋了
- Mom, mom. - Wh-What? Wh-Wh-What?
太好了
All right!
切特  我们找到纳丁了
Chet, we found Nadine.
我们只把她掉到地上过两次
And we only dropped her twice.
你  你们真找到她了
You-you...you found her?
对  她就在这儿
Yes, she's right here.
我的天哪  真是太...  等一下
Oh, my God, that's... Wait a minute.
我不  我不想让他看到我这幅模样
I don't... I'm not sure I want her to see me like this.
这运动服我都穿了三年了  我又发福了
This track suit is 12 seasons old, I've got a gut...
用不着担心  纳丁她也今非昔比了
Oh, don't worry. Nadine's changed, too.
出来吧  切特  求你了
Yeah, come out, Chet, please.
它  她真的很想念你
It-it... she really misses you.
我得想想  你不是说
I don't know. What about all the stuff
我不可能是人体模型吗
you said about how I was never a mannequin?
鲍勃
Bob...
是这样  很抱歉我说了那样的话
Look, um, I'm sorry I said that.
我  我确实认为你需要帮助
I... I do think you need help.
不过在那之前  我们需要你的帮助
But before you get help, we need help.
这么说你还是不相信我咯
So you still don't believe me.
不信  但重要的是
Um, no, but all that matters
你现在是一个爱着人体模型的人类
is you're a man now, in love with the mannequin
而这个模型现在就在我怀里
who I'm holding by the arm
等着你接纳她
but should be in yours.
不得不说  我被这番话打动了
Wow. I got to say that really hit me.
那就好  快开门吧
Okay, so open the door.
你受苦了  宝贝
Tough times, huh, Baby?
我不在意你如今做什么
Well, I don't care what you had to do.
我很想你
I missed you.
我也变了嘛
I've changed. Well...
我喜欢你现在的发型  很...
Yeah, I like your hair that way. It's...
是啊  我...
Uh-huh, yeah. Well, I was...
对
Right.
切特真是个很好的倾诉对象
Chet's a really good listener.
女人很看重这一点
That's important to a woman.
琳  她只是个人体模型
Lin, she's a mannequin.
很明显还是个喋喋不休的人体模型
Who won't shut up, apparently.
两位  抱歉打断你们
Hey, uh, guys, sorry to interrupt.
纳丁有没有说
Did, uh... did Nadine say anything
要恢复橱窗秀的事
about getting that window display going?
因为  我们得来一个重量级的压轴才行
'Cause we... we really need to finish strong here.
你觉得呢  纳丁
What do you think, Nadine?
是啊
Yes.
啥  她  她说什么
What? What is... what is she saying?
她在讲冷笑话呢
She's cracking one of her spoofs.
-什么冷笑话  -她常这样打发时间
- What's a spoof? - Just one of her goof-abouts.
你是说搞笑么  还是
You mean like a joke or...?
纳丁  你还是一样幽默
Nadine, you still got it.
她答应了
Yeah, she wants to do it.
太好了  她讲的什么笑话
That's great. What was the joke?
相信我  你理解不了的
Trust me, you won't get it.
记住  要纹丝不动又栩栩如生
And remember, look alive but absolutely still.
开始
And... no action!
让大家久等了
Uh, thanks for waiting, everyone.
现在为您展出  圣诞特辑
I now give you... Christmas!
确实很值
It was worth it.
莫特  给你拍张照
Mort, I want to take a picture.
调整下假发  不  是你妈妈的
Fix the wig. No, your mom's.
-谁想要礼品券  -小偷
- Okay, who needs a gift certificate? - Thief!
你偷了我的人体模型  还给我
You stole my girl. I want her back!
糟了
Oh, no.
把她给我
Hand her over.
不好意思  她现在跟我了
Sorry. She's with me now.
走着瞧
We'll see about that.
冷静  冷静  兄弟们
Okay, easy. Easy, guys.
世界和平  卖A片的
Yeah, peace on Earth, smut peddler!
马槽危机
Whoa, manger danger! Aah!
好了  别闹了
Come on, stop.
创意很独特嘛
That's a fresh take.
这个基督诞生的场景做得太扯淡了
This creche is crap!
你们该庆幸我没让警察来抓你们这群变态
You're lucky I don't call the cops on you pervs.
你就不能把她卖给我们吗  求你了
Can't we just buy her from you, please?
她是非卖品
She's not for sale.
情趣用品店的老板没有什么是不卖的
Every sex shop owner has his price.
五千
Five grand.
什么  不可能
What? No.
你看...
What about...
两百六十  一  二  三美元如何
two hundred and sixty-one, two, three dollars?
不行  露易丝
No, Louise, that's the money
那是给你们买礼物的钱
we were going to use to buy you kids presents.
那点钱可买不到一间公寓
Okay, that is not enough for an apartment.
我愿意把我的那份贡献出来
You can spend my gift money on Nadine.
是你要的白板啊
Oh, your dry erase board.
也可以用我的那份
You can use my money, too.
你的牙买加雪橇
Oh, your Jamaican bobsled.
好吧  我也加入
Fine. I'm in.
但总统节的礼物要给我补回来
But I better get a heck of a Presidents Day gift.
真的吗  你们都愿意
Seriously? You're all willing
放弃自己的圣诞礼物来帮切特吗
to give up your Christmas presents for Chet?
随便吧  钱给我
What the hell? Give me the money.
-还给你  切特  -谢谢  鲍勃
- Well, here you go, Chet. - Thanks, Bob.
抱歉我们搞砸了你的秀
Sorry we busted up your display.
你为我做了这么多
After everything you did for me.
又给我住  又帮我找回了纳丁
Roof over my head, Nadine back in my arms.
这样吧
All right, you know what?
你明天不用搬走了
You don't need to be out by tomorrow.
真的吗  鲍鲍  你说真的吗
Really, Bobby? You mean it?
是的  过完新年再走吧
Yeah, stay till New Year's.
我来做潘趣酒
Aw. I'll make punch.
不
No!
看  鲍勃  都找到了自己的另一半
Look at us, Bob, with our special ladies, huh?
这样就别无所求了  你说呢
Yeah. We've got it all, right?
我们应该来个四人约会
We should take a trip, the four of us, you know?
我看不必了
Probably not.
我无所谓  去哪儿都行
I'm flexible, wherever you want go.
我  我近期暂时不能出远门
I'm... it-it would be hard for me to get away for a while.
这样  让女士们决定好了
Well, we'll let the ladies figure it out.
百慕大群岛  她有护照吗
Bermuda! Does she have a passport?
我等不了了  切特
I can't wait any more, Chet.
快吻她
Kiss her.
-不  -天哪
- No! - Oh, God.
快捡起来  切特  限时五秒
Pick it up, Chet. Five-second rule.
大家是不是也跟我一样有反应了
Oh, are you as hot as I am right now?
你说你有反应了
Are you hot?
没有  没事了
I'm fine. Never mind.
他们很享受嘛
I think they love it.
天哪  终于要发生了
Oh, my God, it's happening.
这个吻要把她变成人类了
The kiss is turning her human.
不  等等  要把他变回人体模型了
No, wait, it's turning him back into a mannequin.
不  等等  什么都没发生
No, wait, nothing's happening.
也太夸张了  我闪人了
They went too far. I'm out of here.
圣诞快乐  泰迪  假期愉快  莫特
Merry Christmas, Teddy. Happy holidays, Mort.
假期愉快
Happy holidays.
圣诞快乐  各位
Merry Christmas, guys.
下地狱吧  贝尔彻一家
Burn in hell, Belchers!
圣诞节当天
欧叔叔的仓库
Uncle Ernie's storage unit
还是有些奇珍异宝的嘛
had some real treasures after all.
出口指示牌  谢了  圣诞老人
An exit sign. Thanks, Santa.
现在我可以从任何门出去了
Now I can go out any door I want.
我的是鞋码测量器  八码半
I got a shoe sizer. Eight and a half.
我的是商品标签摘除器
I got a tool to remove security tags.
明年圣诞节的礼物我全包了
Next Christmas is on me!
切特
So, Chet...
你从我们这儿离开后打算去哪儿
what are you going to do after we kick you out?
别担心  我们可以回我在曼哈顿的住处
Oh, don't worry. We'll probably stay at my place in Manhattan.
我在那边有个阁楼  正在翻修
I have a loft that was being renovated,
我已经等不及想看它装完后的样子了
and I cannot wait to see how it turned out.
啥
What?!